{
    "Quiz" : [
        {
            "Id" : 1,
            "Question" : "Which of the following functional interface represents a supplier of Boolean-valued results?",
            "Options" : [
                    "BooleanSupplier",
                    "Consumer<T>",
                    "DoubleBinaryOperator",
                    "DoubleConsumer"
            ],
            "Answer" : "BooleanSupplier"
        },
        {
            "Id" : 2,
            "Question" : "Which of the following function of Array object returns true if at least one element in this array satisfies the provided testing function?",
            "Options" : [
                    "reverse()",
                    "shift()",
                    "slice()",
                    "some()"
            ],
            "Answer" : "some()"
        },
        {
            "Id" : 3,
            "Question" : "Which of the following defines a measurement in screen pixels?",
            "Options" : [
                    "px",
                    "vh",
                    "vw",
                    "vmin"
            ],
            "Answer" : "px"
        },
        {
            "Id" : 4,
            "Question" : "A subquery can be placed in which of the SQL clauses?",
            "Options" : [
                    "The WHERE clause",
                    "The HAVING clause",
                    "The FROM clause",
                    "All of the above."
            ],
            "Answer" : "All of the above."
        },
        {
            "Id" : 5,
            "Question" : "Which of the following defines a measurement in picas?",
            "Options" : [
                    "in",
                    "mm",
                    "pc",
                    "pt"
            ],
            "Answer" : "pc"
        },
        {
            "Id" : 6,
            "Question" : "Which of the following is true about the CREATE TABLE statement?",
            "Options" : [
                    "This is a DML statement.",
                    "This statement also record information in the data dictionary.",
                    "You donâ€™t need any privilege to use this statement.",
                    "All of the above."
            ],
            "Answer" : "This statement also record information in the data dictionary.yy"
        },
        {
            "Id" : 7,
            "Question" : "Which of the following defines a measurement relative to a font's x-height?",
            "Options" : [
                    "%",
                    "cm",
                    "em",
                    "ex"
            ],
            "Answer" : "ex"
        },
        {
            "Id" : 8,
            "Question" : "Which of the following selector matches a element based on its id?",
            "Options" : [
                    "The Id Selector",
                    "The Universal Selector",
                    "The Descendant Selecto",
                    "The Class Selector"
            ],
            "Answer" : "The Id Selector"
        },
        {
            "Id" : 9,
            "Question" : "Which of the following is an advantage of using JavaScript?",
            "Options" : [
                    "Less server interaction",
                    "Immediate feedback to the visitors",
                    "Increased interactivity",
                    "All of the above"
            ],
            "Answer" : "All of the above"
        },
        {
            "Id" : 10,
            "Question" : "Which built-in method returns the index within the calling String object of the first occurrence of the specified value?",
            "Options" : [
                    "getIndex()",
                    "location()",
                    "indexOf()",
                    "None of the above."
            ],
            "Answer" : "indexOf()"
        },
        {
            "Id" : 11,
            "Question" : "Which built-in method returns the string representation of the number's value?",
            "Options" : [
                    "toValue()",
                    "toNumber()",
                    "toString()",
                    "None of the above."
            ],
            "Answer" : "toString()"
        },
        {
            "Id" : 12,
            "Question" : "Which of the following function of String object combines the text of two strings and returns a new string?",
            "Options" : [
                    "add()",
                    "merge()",
                    "concat()",
                    "append()"
            ],
            "Answer" : "concat()"
        },
        {
            "Id" : 13,
            "Question" : "Which of the following function of String object returns the characters in a string beginning at the specified location through the specified number of characters?",
            "Options" : [
                    "slice()",
                    "split()",
                    "substr()",
                    "search()"
            ],
            "Answer" : "substr()"
        },
        {
            "Id" : 14,
            "Question" : "Which of the following function of String object returns the calling string value converted to lower case while respecting the current locale?",
            "Options" : [
                    "toLocaleLowerCase()",
                    "toLowerCase()",
                    "toString()",
                    "substring()"
            ],
            "Answer" : "toLocaleLowerCase()"
        },
        {
            "Id" : 15,
            "Question" : "Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be displayed as a superscript, as if it were in a <sup> tag?",
            "Options" : [
                    "sup()",
                    "small()",
                    "strike()",
                    "sub()"
            ],
            "Answer" : "sup()"
        }
    ]
}